So here we go welcome back once again the view
is spectated watching us live ma se mitra
Solanki I am welcoming you all good evening and we will
welcome
match Loughton vs UIB
India
Mangesh and
Aniket Kathan Purohit start proceedings
from UIB
India cracking shot the field is
running so couple of runs taken the
four ball five runs
one yahan pe khel diya hai excellent
shot outside seamerg it went for four runs
you can see the action
replay absolute good shot is played and the field is at the right
region for four
runs last ball coming up
of the first
over it is cracking hit cracking shot the fielder is
at the right region this time coming back for
two so couple of runs two and this happened after one over
on 11 a lock
ton welcome back once again IC Lombard
Brokers Premier
League first
day after this just have couple of matches
left for the completion of day one
great energy great
power have some names on my mind Priyanshu
Jain batting well  Mangesh
Jagtap couple of good
bowling from Akash Jadhav the spin attack
left arm spin was really fantastic some of many
memories will still be on the mind
bowling is here Rohit
Nimbalk no 11
fw ball full delivery but outside off line
signalling wide ball umpire misses Om Singh takes
one of the finest side
this time plays towards long of a couple of overs
to the total lock ton one de two
14 on
one Aniket and
Mangesh this time good bowling swing and miss
totally beaten here batsman wanted to take a run
sent back
1.3 14 fw lock
ton good effort there long fielder was
trying to take a catch if he had taken a
dying catch it would have come
1.4 16
fw lock ton score of two runs
full toss ball played this
in long area and once again two
runs will be added here in over throw
three runs will be added here
1.5 19
Luck Rohit  Nimble conceded a run in over
first over, but failed to go
for a
wide, totally looking to play for the big
one, completely missed the action replay,
new batsman comes in at three, the
chase will move forward with two runs, then Mangesh was run
out
on the last ball, eight four
balls, what is the update, scorer
so we have the updated score card on the
board, running 22 for
luck, Mayur
Lohar, just single played at point
region, 2.3, two on 23, here the score of lock ton
swing, miss, big shot, attempt, mane,
totally beaten, batsman
good bowling performance here, Mayur Lohar,
two on one, two on 2,
this time played in the long area,
going for two runs, excellent
running, more runs will be obtained in the overthrow,
what is the umpire's call
out, run out, just short of the crease,
good throw from point end, keeper has done
the job, or we can have luck, run out, just short of the crease, good
throw from long
region, the non-scorer
2.4 Dinesh takes
a cracking shot,
fielder takes a wide long run, coming
back for three runs, good
running 2.5 28 for three, lock ton,
last ball by Kishore, Mayur takes off,
out of the stumps, umpire Mr Om Singh
signals wide
ball, two overs off,
three swings, misses, big shot
attempt, over ends with a dot ball, 29 runs after three overs, lock ton for three runs, after three overs,
29 runs after three wickets, 29 runs after three overs, 3 runs after three wickets, 29 runs after three overs, lock
ton for three runs, after three overs,
29 runs after three wickets, 29 runs after three overs,
lock score
now coming up, the final over of the first,
cracking shot, coming back for two, a
bit of a run, run by the fielder and batsman
taken a
double 3.1
3143 Dinesh Garv and
Ankush batsmen on the pitch, on the crease,
take a four delivery, good
bowling 3.2 31 for four, last four balls  Coming
up
single run last three balls lock ton a big
hit or UIB
India will be
looking to take a wicket this is what Rohit
Nimbalk excellent bowling performance
Rohit
Nimbalk has given away only three runs in this over
four
balls last two balls Coming up of the first
innings lock ton 32
first swing
miss
variation release the
ball with slow pace here
bowling performance with finesse back
to back dot
balls last ball now of the innings Coming
up
so retired out now Kunal Tanna three for the
last
ball 32 3.5 last ball first
innings no man's
land wanted to go for the second yes no yes no you will get
runs here two more runs stolen here
people steal hearts these batsmen
steal runs
so end of the innings so
three runs taken last ball
and two runs taken so four overs over
three UAE need 36 runs to win the match
score so let's take a short break and come back stay
tuned but no
ball still the match  On first
innings free hit
ball cracking strike looking for two more
runs and
asking for another one but a couple of runs not to end
finally four overs play is over 38 off three
tons and UIB India
need 39
runs to win See you again after a short break
In the game of life stay protected
with ICICI Lumbard health insurance
In the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lumbard health insurance
In the game
of life stay protected with
ICICI Lumbard health insurance
Hello and welcome back once again we are back in
action 39 to chase your UIB
India first ball looking to play for the big
one suddenly so many fielders have come on the pitch
one ball bowled one for no run
Mayur
Lohar took a single Rohit Nimbalak took
strike and Mangesh started from
first over Power play only to field Id
circle taken a couple of runs
not easy to take the high  Catch the high catch went very much high
top
edge very well
tried by the
fielder and batsman survive Rohit took the ball
late two balls later three runs no wicket
UIB India have a target of 39 to win
this time they have played in the gap they have
sent it outside off Simmer excellent
fours played like Adam Gilak shot absolute
fantastic one of the
finest strikes Gilak in the
commentary box in many
overseas what strike what head it bangs the
roof top six
absolute
fantastic when the name of Adam Gilak is taken the
enthusiasm in him doubles there is
enthusiasm there is passion there is power there is spirit there is
excellent bat the roof the roof top
six very good
batting the lefty batting has a different style
Rohit Nimbalak is very
special four balls bowled 13 for no wicket five
balls bowled 13 runs on
board toss and the block hole good come back from
Mangesh only single
run so rotating the strike after hitting
boundary after hitting six the single run
Rohit  Nabakar firing batting 1 4 14 and no
25 runs are needed now in the coming 19 balls
14 runs should come in this side last ball Mangesh
on strike yes no yes
no and the
over will end with a single run
so one gun 15 for no loss 24 to get from
15 runs after one over no wicket Kunal
Tanna comes to bowl will
go for the second run good running
between the wickets Mayur and
Rohit
1.1 17 no wicket
this time have played it
in the direction of self will be satisfied with one run
21 runs needed 16
balls Rohit Nimbalk Ro hit Nimbalk non
strike
this time Rohit once again hit hard
but with one run good fielding there
is a fielder deployed in the deep to save the run
try to take the wicket now the
Black Army team of the locks have
pulled this time the
fielder threw there and there
is a chance here
but one run
shot only one run no wicket at 1.4 20
19 runs needed
balls Badi edge and this is it out
Wanted to play a big
shot Good bowling Good lawn
Wanted to play with the turn Got behind
First wicket falls
So lock ton strikes First wicket of
ye
India 1.52
Fav Now 19 to get an coming 1 ball left
The fielder the catcher
Keeper Prasanna
So dot ball to End of the over After two overs
20 for
one Now need 19 runs in two overs
So ye watching IC Lord Brokers Premier
League 205 The Day
One More three matches left and a couple of matches
left after this match Day
one is
on and we will have the day two Sunday Funday
now Anand Upadhyay into the attack On
first ball Went for a dot
ball Two the one for 20 One
Tried here
but only a single Run at long
off 2.2 21 Fav 18 to get from 10 balls
18 runs 10 balls
Good bowling Direct hit something to win the match for UI India  Could
[music]
and Runs will come
overthrow two runs scored 2.3 for 16 to get
from nine balls now let
's play towards point region for only a
single run
15 runs needed eight balls
left for India to win this match one just outside off side
line white see
good left by Rohit
Nimbalk so with well left one more wide one more
not dead
14 Runs 1
p2 Anand Upadhyay considered his
quality bowling
went big
one and it's
taken his chance
big
wicket big wicket here it fell
japak it's changing over turning out something
special Anand Upadhyay very good bowling
just five runs and managed to take a wicket and the
big fish fell in the water
chhapak we were talking about this wicket and that wicket has been taken by the
brave
player of Lawton Ankush has taken it a
brilliant
catch after three overs two for 25 last over
coming on 14 to get
excellent last over only five runs one wicket
Anand Upadhyay this match  Changed it and
made it dramatic.
Tried to hit the shot but could not time it.
Runs will come in the form of leg before.
Five balls 13
runs have been cut lightly.
Wanted to take two runs but
gave one run on strike.
Four balls 12
runs to Abhishek Sawant. Into the block hole. This is good
bowling. Only single
run. 11 runs needed. Three balls
left. Good bowling here. Kunal Tanna
1.3 runs. One wicket. Now coming up. Last
three balls 11 runs to get.
Played towards maiden for single run.
So Abhishek sound retired. The new batsman
replaces Gaurav Gurav.
This time he has played the ball.
Wanted to go for the second run.
Fielder fumbled a little there and the batsman
took a
double here. Now a ball is needed. 8 runs are needed.
White ball, no
ball, four delivery by Kunal
Tanna and with a dot ball here,
this match has been won by seven runs.
Lock
ton is important. The second last over to be played
is a key for the
victory. Anand Upadhyay.  over five runs one
wicket the previous over worked and moved towards the win
so what a great tournament we had till now
and coming up in the game of life stay
protected with ICICI Lord Health
Insurance
in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance
so hello and we will come back once again
ICICI Lord Brokers Premier League
2025 has got a great start today first
day Raghunath
Titans after this two more
matches and the first day will be over again
Sunday Funde will
blow the cricket ke
Dande Manikant Singh on strike Varun
Patil on non-strike he starts Karanar
Dheeraj
Sonane let's play Ravi go tov
so Adam Insurance Brokers Limited one the
toss let to bowl
first ball single run into the account of
Raghunath Titans
one more single
run and
gun short cover
fielder
catch celebration here
Adam Insurance Brokers
Limited we have one more Orange Army now its
first wicket falls very Ali falls first it all
Rakhna Titans looking to play
for  Big one simple catch taken at short
cover
so catch taken by
upper three balls ball two for one Chetan
Kumar now
on strike full toss ball played it there
is fielder in the swell direction one run quickly
sent back Daulia one run run taken
four balls bowled the four good start from
Adam
Brockers just a single very good fielding
there at deep
region five balls only four runs one wicket
good start by Adam Brockers is
it an outside edge or a
four bye
for four runs
you can see this ball coming off the bat action replay yes
outside edge absolutely outside edge and the
wicket keeper could not catch it it hit the main banner
and these four
runs so one was gone at for one run
nal titles
so Aparv Meta
comes into attack on strike Varun Patil Patil
wanted to play a strong ball safe landing only single
run one the one run one runna titus's
score is excellent first
day
continues typical tap shot box
cricket one the two 10 runs one wicket loss
Varun Patil and  Chetan Kumar Chetan Kumar
into the block hole this time to play towards
lunge on for a single
run 1.31
feb this time a slow release but to outside side
of tum just umpire signalling white
ball umpire Mr Prashant Regi here so very good
bowling this time good come
back by Apari
Mahata one on the ch 12
one has played this one in the direction of sway
only a single
run will have to be seen whether they will go for some big hitting in the next over
or not Raksha Titans will
set a target here for a big score
for Adam Insurance
good stop has he caught it has caught it has stopped it
or is it
out the
magic ball stuck in his hands as if it was in his hands
Favi quick wicket ki
pat number two two overs 1 run any
loss of wicket Raksha that score
direct hit and this is a
direct hit and this is a good
strike from the fielder there
to
play as soon as possible your cooperation is
required thank you very
much two overs after 13 for
two Nikhil Chauhan
Naveen Phalandaj
comes  Batting
and Nikhil Chavan has come to bowl and
Sandeep Pawar is batting, bowler Nikhil Chavan is batting and
Sandeep
Pawar has two on two, three on 15, Raghunath
Titans have bowled well there,
Atom Insurance has
played 15 balls, three on 15, straight down the ground,
so after three overs, three on 18, Raghunath Dad
coming up, the final over of the first,
pace of the match,
move ahead as soon as possible, too much left,
R Soni comes into
attack, only
single, good bowling performance, Adam
Rains, ball to ball, score,
last
over and a very simple catch in his hands, as if a
Moti Chur
laddu has been handed over to him,
simple catch taken,
gun 19, for Raghunath Titans,
Rohit has taken this catch, 3.2,
four on 19, who will win and who will lose,
what pass call, is it out or
not, is it
run out, 3.31, for coming up, last
three
balls, Gautam Soni comes  To the crease
laggar
they have to finish quickly and leave dinner
time 3.41 for 6 excellent bowling performance
Adam Insurance
last two balls first innings
speed up as soon as possible two matches are left we have to come tomorrow as well we have to
win
so let's gun for the final ball
six very good
shot Faisal Khan has done something amazing some
fun some runs came on the board after four overs
26 overs Adam Insurance have to score
only 27 runs in four overs we will be back after a short break in
the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance
in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance in
the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance
so just 27 runs and four balls bowled no less once again
welcome
back Melvin Thomas and Jairaj Singh Manik More are very much high
no feeder there and ball will go no oh very
good
stop excellent work at  Which
reason? Wait signal yet very good
feeding so three runs taken, foul ball bowled at
for no loss What will the last ball do?
Jayraj
Manik on strike brilliantly the ball goes over the seamer
in the constellation for six runs
Ranking
shot over the over with six runs After one over
14 for no loss Now only 13 runs are
needed Now finish this match in the next three balls So the
second match should start as soon as possible
Just 13 to get and let's see now Adam
Insurance
cracking shot Jayraj Singh has
played this time the ball is going in the direction of the square It will
not stop outside the boundary There is a
fielder on the ball there
Going for the second run
Three runs
taken No
wicket at 1.21 Only 10 runs
are needed
Now 2.4 to go 16
balls excellent
effort If he had taken this catch it would have been the catch of the
tournament so far What good effort
Diving effort Can see action
Replay Good effort Ba feed Ka reason Couple of runs
taken
and here it is  Gets out Trying to hit a big shot
Fall of the first wicket Jayraj Cotton bowled Faisal Khan No run Five
balls hit a maximum Eight runs needed
14 balls left Adam
Ishwar starts well Strong start in the first over
runs So watching ICC Lombard Rockers
Premier
League Day One after this we have more couple of
matches left for the Day One completion
Nikhil Chavan comes
on strike Only a single run
Attempts to hit a big shot and the connection was not
found Timing was not right Run
comes in the form of leg bye End of over
after two overs 21 runs for the loss of one wicket
Just one big hit six runs for the victory
Adam
Ishwar comes in first 14 runs Then comes seven runs Now
six runs are needed off the
ball and now
only five runs are
needed Single run no just four to get win
this
match Easy win
so just one run required for the match to win
and finish off in
style We will go the way four runs at the corner
region at the end  of the match Adam
Insurance Brokes Limited one by no
wickets
Coming up second last match
still game is on ICICI Lombard Brokes
Premier League stay tuned yet
audience two more matches to
left for day
one Coming up the next match Howden vs
UIB India and then after Adam
Insurance once again against Unila
Strikers
iss journey me ab aakhri do match hai baki raat
baki baat baki
Howden and UIB India get ready
in the game of life stay protected
vs ICICI Lombard Health Insurance in
the game of life stay protected vs
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance once again
welcome back all the yet done watching us
live great game today what a
fantastic once again
welcome second last match day one
UIB India one toss led to Bal
Ramakrishnan on strike Mitesh Patil on
non-strike Tan Purohit young blood young
talented seven number jersey Thala for region
will start
proceedings yes we talk about young blood young
talent here is my talent Katan  Purohit
first ball
strike sent back big batsman
Ramakrishnan absolute good bowling from Katan
Purohit first wicket fall very
early so howden lost the first wicket
first ball didn't for one he took a
hat-trick now Katan
Purohit so beautiful so magical so clever so
powerful just looking like he was absolutely
fantastic what start couple of
wickets very early on first two balls
sent back what start
Katan
Purohit takes the jersey black for reason wicket
for
reason he is on hat-trick
now waiting for the
hat-trick first hat-trick of the tournament
will take lets see
first two balls won golden duck batsman
chance for one more golden
duck what start second last match
of day one so
Aniket Kerkar on strike he went for a hat-
trick
ball so time played towards mid-wicket reason coming back second second ball they lost the
couple
taken so the account started off howden with
run boy totu hown
looking to play sweep
shot  Umpire single by Mr Om
Singh Umpire C by Mr Om Singh
signalling high
five balls ball the for
two cracking shot over the fielder at covers
clears the infield will go for four
comfortable boundary deep extra cover see
Mar ka g bar this went
four five balls seven and two wickets have come back
Howden in this over first two balls
wickets
then two runs then single then four story of this over
will do the last ball narration
Purohit could not collect there the
ball went what happened there and it has been stopped
suddenly Ronaldo
sometimes one has to adopt football skill
in cricket goal saved boundary saved over
ends with three runs
after one over two for 10 Howden
what a game what a start couple of wickets now come back how done
team
t and the first power
play no Rohit
Nimbalk into the
attack good bowling there swing
emis and a good one here let's
talk completely about the first day of today very
good
all the players excitement crowd  The
excitement and management was very
good
and for the first day we have now let the second last match go in
progress.
Good ball in the wicket keeper's gloves. Rohit Nimbalak. You have to leave
the game. Leave the moment once a
year. This moment will never come back.
We can't wait for a big
sixer. Absolutely fantastic action.
Replay but down the track and very well
played. Long shot of sir.
Six runs from here on.
Two one,
three swing, no, good come back from here.
Rohit Laker has an
excellent strike. Mitesh Patil is
playing on 13. Six balls and no,
good bowling. Good come back.
First ball is a dot. Second ball is a dot. Then
third ball is a six. Fourth ball is a dot. Five balls are a
dot. The story of this over will be the last ball.
Rohit
Nimbalak is setting the fielding.
Sent it to deep extra cover. Could
not judge the catch. No problem,
you have tried, you have tried very hard. The
ball went very high and with two runs
Mitesh Patil and Aniket
Kerkar ran fast after two overs.  Two on 18 Howden
18 fat to how done coming up next two overs
will they get more n
plus so they 36 to
score and they get 40 plus score in four
overs
Mayur Jan na stuck it
into the block
hole second wanted to go excellent throw at the non
strike end
2 on 19 fat to score Mitesh Patil
this time is played towards wide long only
a
single will try now Aniket and Mitesh
Patil will try to set a big score
full toss ball and it was sent outside the C Marg
it went for four we were talking about trying and
trying should continue because you will get as much as you
want if you don't try then you will become
tied fish
tried and hit a four sent it across the
boundary
two Dati 2 on 24
Howden this time the ball is going with speed in the backward region towards
fine
outside the seamer and a powerful
four tremendous batting
performance Aniket
Kerkar section Khan and Dhani Sokar back to
back 2.4  Score on 28 for two, Howden
stand and deliver and once again hat-trick of
boundaries, make some nose round, applause to
Aniket Kerkar, someone please
clap, back to back four
fours and then
now on the last ball,
he is batting with a different style,
so back to back four fours, four
fours.  After three overs, 18 runs came at 36.
Coming up from this over, the
last one was just talking about
crossing 40, 40 plus.
So he scored 36 runs.
This is batting. This is power. This is enthusiasm. This is passion.
Aniket Kerkar 20 runs. Seven balls. Four
fours. Mitesh Patil 16 balls. One one six.
Three overs at 36. Howden.
Outside edge. Fielder stopped the shot there. The
ball would move forward with one run.
This time he played it in the air. He
sent it to the fielder. Just a shot of long. Fielder ran for
two runs. He ran quickly for two runs.
39. Fattu
Howden pulled the short pitched ball
and made the ball go across for four runs.
Cracking shot. He made room and sent it
across for four runs.
Excellent batting performance. Aniket
Kerkar 26
balls. Five
boundaries. This is his power. This
enthusiasm. He stunned the opposition team.
This time good bowling. Fuller
delivery. Dot ball. Good come back.
Rohit  3.4 43 ft. Coming up last two balls
of the first innings
swing miss looking to play it
out so wicket falls coming up the final ball 43
ft. Now
howdun looking for a big connection trying to take a run
here it is done at
suman wicket
keeper n dl p 4343 howdun now
coming up the final ball of the first
innings lets see if a can
get one big hit so
target will be 50 once again he has to
go for a run up it is wide
signal l so taken a single
run to
extras new batsman at non
strike and aniket
kerkar on strike
cracking shot ball won right fielder cant get it so
good and finally got about 4950
and the target is 50 to win uib india
absolutely fantastic great shot very well played
makes some nose run up anil aniket
kerkar 30 runs from 12 balls
four four overs
4943 50  UIB India aim to
meet again after a short break
In the game of life Stay protected
with ICICI Lombard Health Insurance
In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance In the
game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance
Hello a welcome back once
again 50 to win four
overs Rohit nil strike Mayur Lohar on non-
strike Vishal
Jadhav
starts 50 runs 24 balls let's play
first ball in block
hole inside edge and starts with a rung
One ball but one no loss ULB
India now Mayur
Lohar on strike
49 runs
3.5 overs good
stop at point region
so the target of 52 chase Rohit and Mayur
opening pair from UIB
India looking for a big one good bowling good
start Vishal Jadhav
first over very good
start i b f no loss ULB India 47 get
33 very good stop at can
Reason quick single no taken double run
taken very good running Rohit and Mayur ran
very fast Gujarat
Express also failed in front of them
here opportunity was taken on one pitch catch
five balls six runs no wicket UIB
India There was
something different about childhood, that era was different
we used to play cricket with Jat and we used to turn the ball quickly
this time good
bowling finishes the over with a dot ball
excellent shot excellent start Vishal Jadhav
one over six runs no wicket here score
UIB India 44 runs to get from over
left this is what the quality
start done by
Howden now another good economical
over Howden's team will go towards victory in this match
but Rohit Nimbalk will say
I am here
we will definitely try to make runs
Rama Krishnan comes into the
attack after no
loss you are watching ICICI
Lord Brokers Premier League
2025 Day One in progress
so see no loss 1.1 YB India 43
runs to get in 2.5 overs
it's very  Good bowling, this is quality, this is
super class, this is fantastic, this is
magical, big bowling run up, Ramakrishnan, good
line, length, excellent bowling attack, this is what
quality bowling
is required, this flip shot, play towards deep, backward slack, coming back for two, 1.39 for no run, India target of 50 here, this time just a single, no 1.4, 10 runs, no wicket, 40 runs needed in the coming 14 balls, two big hits in this
over,
Rohit
Sharma, the Adam Gilchrist in him will wake up now
and what happened, the catch was dropped, a dream was
broken, there was an opportunity to catch it here, you
can see the replay, straight pouch ball and fielder
present,
dropped
catch in the direction of S, one wicket on the last ball, 11, no wicket,
oh what has happened, oh Lord, Hari Ram
Krishna Jagannath Premanand, what happened, the
catch was dropped on the left side, the catch was dropped on the right side,
luck slipped from his hands,
two wickets could have been taken here, there was another chance in
two overs  After 12 no wickets
UIB India not 38 runs to get in Coming in two
overs 19 runs still the match is
on very tough now to chase 19 runs per over
Rohit Nimbalk Myer Lohar having a chat how they will
perform how they will bat how they will prove that you are very
right
After two overs no wickets at 12 sot overs
12 for no loss UIB India
coming
up motu over 38 to
get his gun high in the air caught to catch to call
safe
landing and call couple of runs
taken runny like a fire still many more to go
36 to get from 11
balls outside leg line white sill ba
umpire Mr Sachin takes
two the one no wickets at 15 35 runs
and balls left 11
blocks no chance in the hall
good bowling performance to hit big shots
Vishal Yadav Sangli Kamagiri Sangli
Bowling Rohit Nimbalk is on strike trying to
hit two big shots  Try from the
lake side region, there
is still a chance 34 runs, 10
balls have been played this time,
good fielding, wat stop
deep mid wicket,
one run, only one run
at 2.31, no wicket here,
wide ball and run will be found, will
still try, 33 runs, no
ball, UIB
India will definitely try
but there is no chance this time, the
ball has been lifted in the air, is there a fielder present, will he catch it, yes, he has caught it, got caught,
out,
fall of wicket, number one UIB India
2.41, for one,
you can see, went to take the action replay,
here the timing was not right and a
great catch,
perhaps that replay was not recorded,
two overs on 18,
tried to play a different shot but the
ball went outside, wide ball
2.4 19, for UIB
India into the black hole, not giving any chance,
with one run the car will move forward here,
30 runs, now seven balls to come, a big
hit here, it remains to be seen what Rohit Sharma will do, will create a blast,
swing, good
bowling, end of the over, three overs, 20 runs  One
wicket needed in one over 30 runs
so 20
for coming
up here
now 3.12
for defense played but already it's the match of
Howden
four balls
left 21 Feb 29 to get coming
four
balls tuts cracking hit tus gun long way we was
waiting for this moment absolute
fantastic for
six cracking shot six
runs umpire signals six
runs 3.3 27 Feb 23 from
3.3 27 But the last three
balls are being decorated in fielding and
you have won this match
then bowl three deliveries and finish the match but the
important thing here is that the net run rate is
also very important
that's why every ball is
important this time good bowling played this shot
walking single on square leg the
fielder
tried it but there was some commotion there was some noise
something else happened two runs
taken
3.5 30 at UIB
India
last ball of this match
and here only one run  And this match has been
finished, that's a
good batting performance. Now coming up, the
last match of day one, don't go anywhere, there's still
the single match, a final match of the
first day. Coming up, Adam Insurance
Brokers Ltd. vs Uni Lite
Strikers,
stay tuned for the next match
in the game of life, stay protected with
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance in
the game of life, stay protected vs
ICICI Lord Health Insurance.
So hello and welcome back once again,
final match of day one, league match, Uni
Lite Strikers vs Adam Insurance
Brokers Ltd., one. The toss
is elected to
bat. So, first day, final match, this performance is what's happening.
League final match of day one, Madhav Kadam will
be on strike, Mahesh Shetty on non-
strike, and
Dheeraj
Sunani will start here. Let's start, umpire checking
with the
scorers. Let's play, here we go. First
ball, four, o's game, strange, amazing game, cricket,
this game, unique match, out side. The let's start
with a wide ball, zero balls later, no wicket on one.
Uni Lite Strikers
this time, a great single run straight to the fielder.
Quick single
taken by Madhav Kadam with one run off the mark
strike Mahesh Shetty one ball two runs
no wicket what a day it has been a great day
brilliant bang proud
dug out our yat audience all the management
excellent excitement hi excitement
proper weekend vibes now coming to end with this one
match left ts very good shot very
well played fielder tried a long off
fielder throw kar dya hai and with two runs
here the score will move forward
two balls bowled for no
loss and this is the moment you to enjoy every time
you play cricket it's time to
work off you have a
good day tiring day not weekend
it's time to
refresh so it will be fresh up once you log in
on Monday
so one more day coming up today tomorrow will be very much more
interesting what we saw
today it will be the excitement will be double something now
with the 8 fielder
there it will say take some time to hit oh okay fine let's
play continue
so  Next tomorrow's
match next day Sunday will be more
exciting because this qualifier round
will be
on three balls bowled five for no
loss full toss ball is played the fielder is
at covers he stops he collects he throws
single run
four balls six runs no wicket Uni
light strikers
after winning the toss
decided to field in insurance will chase good
start only seven runs first five
balls
ICICI Lombard
Brokers Premier League
2025 first day last
match wide ball Mr Prashant Rege
signaling
five balls eight runs no wicket Uni light
strikers
after bowling the ball a little direction turned down the
wicket root changed the fielder got confused will get
one run after one over nine runs
no wicket Uni light
strikers fantastic day many
names to call out
appreciation Orange
Army Sunny sir performed
well in the bat in the fielding then
Mangesh
Jagtap Mukund ji came to our commentary box
last year as well and this year
also then we have Akash Jadhav spin bowling
king  Some Many Names To Be Called Out For The
Appreciation Endless Performance
Spectacular And Fabulous Crowd What A
Support Thank You Very Much Supporting Me
Also And The Excitement Will Be More Double
Tomorrow We Will Be Back Tomorrow Around 8M
9M The Match Will
Start So You Can Subscribe This Channel
And Press The Bell Icon So When Ever The
Event Will Start Of Tomorrow You Will Get
Notified You Just Don't Have To Wait For The
Link You Have To Subscribe And Press The
Bell Icon So You Get The Notification Once The
Match Will Start Very Easy For
You Now It's On Your
Hand So One More This Time Got A Wicket Catch
Taken First Wicket Fallen Taken The Catch 1.1
941 Uni Light Strikers
Aparv Mehta First
Ball Swing In Miss Very Good
Bowling Message From Mahesh Rahul 1 The Do No
Run One Wicket Loss
Uni Light Strikers
1.29 On One
Iss Baar Khel Diya
Hai Ek Dati 10 On One Uni Light Strikers
Aparv Mehta
Mahesh Strike
Swing  The ball went outside the stumps, signalling a wide ball, one
at 1.31, one at Uni Light Strikers will
try, now we will see this, Apoorv
Mehta, wicket on the first ball, then a dot ball, then a
single and a
wide swing in, miss, huge appeal
there, bund
stumps, complete pressure on the umpire, one
at 1.41, one at Uni Light Strikers
and this time he has sent it,
good shot, excellent shot,
it went four outside the boundary, he has
sent it with good timing, you
can see the action
replay, made space, sent it towards the final,
four
runs, one at 1.51, one at Uni Light Strikers,
Apoorv Mehta, you need some changes in fielding,
change in fielding settings with a different style, one at 1.51, one at 1.51, one at 1.51, he has
played in the gap, fielder is present
there,
couple of runs taken, so end of the number two, 17
for Uni Light Strikers,
two overs at 17, now in the last two overs,
what will they do, something different, what will they do, something
better,
Mahesh and
Rahul, two overs at 17, one at Uni Light
Strikers,
this time he has lifted the ball in the air and has
caught it, the catch is excellent  Catches Catches Wins
Matches Fall of wickets here
you can see the action replay
wanted to take and these are the outs Catches Wins Matches
2.1 Two excellent catches on 1 Apoorv Mehta
in covers 2.17 for Uni Light Strikers
2.2 Two for 18 Score here Uni Light
Strikers Takes
ball going outside the stump
Prashant Rege from among the umpires signalled wide
ball 19 runs two wickets loss Uni Light
Strikers
2.2 This time the ball went very high in the air
what is the result it went out of the boundary
four explosive four runs Ts got four
You can see the action
replay good effort
but fielder is out of the boundary for four runs
2.3
Two Uni Light Strikers
Wt umpire's call
late inside the crease
comfortable
2.4 Two for 25 Uni Light Strikers
Nikhil Sawa 8 runs one wicket in this over
in the previous over Upar Mantha 8 runs one
wicket 2.4 Two for 25
Mahesh Shetty 16 eight balls two fours
toss  Ball has played this
and he is out Wicket keeper
number
three You can see the action
replay Catch SNS
Matches Sots Wicket fall number three
2.5 25
Fth Mahesh Shetty Caught Ashish Bowled Nikhil 16
Off Ny Ball to Fors
2.5 25 Off Three Unila Strikers
This time he has lifted the ball in the air Fielder
is present and a
catch Catch
practice Final of today's league match
Three overs over in the final game Four for 25
Back to back Nikhil
Bowled very well Three wickets taken in this over
And eight
runs were spent Wicket on the first ball Then the last
two balls Three overs over
25 Four Who will win Who will lose
25 Off Three Last over of this first innings
Unila Strikers
25 4th gun Coming up the final over Who will
bowl the final
over Apurv Meta
takes a cracking hit in the air Fielder
tried and coming back for two Was called
comfortable inside the crease Couple of runs
taken 3.1  27 for Unila Strikers
last five balls first
innings
3.17 for
four this time a powerful hit by the
fielder
missed the attempt there the dream was
shattered 3 for two 29 four back to back two
runs
Unila Strikers batsmen are progressing slowly with last four
balls Coming up of the first innings
very good bowling swing in miss this
first day of ICI Lombard Brokers Premier League 2025 now the last
match tomorrow we will
meet once more in the qualifier rounds
tomorrow is going to be a very exciting day
this time good bowling no chance in the block hole
3.4 for four back to back dot
balls final over now
Apurv
Mehta is bowling well another dot ball what a thing back to back
three dots excellent
bowling good economical bowling last over of this
first innings one ten five 12 runs one wicket
spent Apurv Mehta now last ball of the
first innings coming
up this time he has pulled the
fielder present in the corner will run for two runs
and with two runs  With this the over
ends the game of four overs is over 31 for four
who will win and who will win
see you after a short break Adam
Insurance Brokers now have to score 32
runs in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance in the
game of life stay protected with ICICI
Lord Health Insurance
in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance in the game
of life stay protected with Lombard
Health Insurance
hello and welcome back once again the chase Adam
Insurance will chase the target
of 32 runs Ravi goes first
ball
Kedar Melvin Thomas on strike Jairaj
Singh on non
strike so coming up
the final match in progress of day one league
match ICICI Lombard Brokes Premier
League we are heading towards
league day one final match now the second
innings Suss Green bowled into the black hole what a
good bowling excellent
stuff Kedar into the black hole no chance for
the batsman to
hit and Jairaj Singh got you
can  See the action replay
York delivery excellent clean bowled
gun so Jayraj Singh without troubling the score
golden duck two balls bowled one for one Adam
Insurance
now the new batsman Nikhil
Chavan three balls two for one Adam Insurance
looking oh my god what an energy what a
power athletic Kedar totally excellent here
not sparing himself
good here
this is effort this
is power big match big league will try here
and see this effort this is what happens cricket is all about no
one cares about your life no
one cares about injury you keep playing
and keep playing
this strategy of cricketer 45 n
jersey
bowling action very good
action single run this
time looking to play straight down ground
protection down long off long
on five balls bowled the for last ball of the
first over coming up 29 to get from 3.1
now will the runs come in the form of leg bye
no here the ball hits the bat and the
over ends with one run excellent start
here good bowling by Uni Lat Strikers
four runs one wicket after one over
28 runs are needed in three overs to come at a loss,
so after one over for far, Ed
Rains and Mahesh Shetty into the bowling
attack, one big over in this over coming up at least they can reach
15 for so they can get more
15 runs in another two
overs, this will strategy to power Nikhil
Chauhan and Melvin
Thomas Day One This is the last
match still many matches to come Qualifier
round semi-final match final match
important tomorrow Sunday will be the more
excitement so to get more
excitement you can
subscribe this channel and press the bell icon
so once the stream is on you will get
notified JFS
channel so to make it easy you just subscribe to the channel
and press the bell icon as soon as the
stream starts you will get a notification
this match day has started on this second
day at 1.26 this time a great shot has been pulled,
fielder is present there, there may be a little
fumble here due to D factor, there may be a
little slip
at 1.38 by
an admin
Runs 24 runs and 15
balls, we were talking about reaching that 15 runs,
in this over he has pulled a short pouch ball, it went, the
ball changed direction, the time changed the mood suddenly,
what happened there, he has
fielded, he has taken three runs,
you can see the action replay very well, he
slipped down a little there,
how many runs should he take, this will have to be seen here, we are
checking at 1.38, we are confirming,
runs taken 1.4, one on 11,
21 runs, 2.2
overs, 14 balls, 21 runs, anything can happen, the pass can
turn at any time, this time he has lifted the
ball in the air, the feeder is present and what a
missed dream, it was a broken
opportunity here,
you can miss such opportunities,
see this time he has played,
two runs have been scored, yes,
two runs, the end of the over, we were talking about, we have almost
reached 15 runs,
after two overs, one on 14, in the next two
overs, we need 18 runs,
12 balls, 18 runs is not much there  But dug
out in
shout twos 14 for one left 18 to get this will be a
very important over
in the coming time
now excellent bowling here
very close
stumps 2.1 14 for one 18 runs 11
balls this over now if Kedar bowls an economical over then
Ull Strikers can come back in this match
good fielding has been played only
single
run two the two 15 for one Adam Insurance
this time has lifted the ball in the air the ball
slipped from the hands of the fielder present there
tried to catch it there
2.3 17 for one Adam Insurance the team will move
forward with two runs United
Strikers are chasing the runs in ad after four overs on 31
32 15 runs no ball good stop in follow through
Ketar is completely
explosive bowling here into the block hole trying to
keep this match in their control United Strikers ball
going outside leg stump the keeper has
missed it this run will come
and what will be the signal of the umpire wide ball  Mr.
Navsad
at 2.41, an Adam Insurance
swing misses, attempt to hit a big shot,
connection was not found, timing was not right,
good bowling, there we were talking about Kedar
bowling economically in this over,
good bowling, will come back this match,
13 runs in 7 balls,
see this, runs have come, oh look what is
happening,
this is a small
error, how many runs did you give away for free,
a simple throw and see this, you gave a wide
ball and two
runs, 10 runs were needed, three runs came,
total 10 runs in 7 balls,
this is now the turning point of the match, more runs
came,
this time good comeback, see this, good
comeback has also been done, and with this the over will
end, one over is left, 10 runs are needed to
win this match, Adam
Insurance, so this is the first day of ICICI Lombard Brokes
Premier League
2025,
now the last match, league match
and the last over,
now
runs are left, one more is left,
Melvin Thomas, Nikhil Chauhan will do something amazing,
something will be a
blast, Naush ji has to play something different  Cricket
bowling practice Umpires are doing
Three overs 22 for one Adam Insurance Now
coming up the final over of this match 10 runs to get over
Can win this match but a quality
bowling The previous over three runs considered he was
bowling well but wide
balls Completely lost the rhythm
so three was gone 22 for one Let's move
towards the match Three overs 22 for
two Last over 10
runs Who will win this match Who will lose this match The
time to come you
see here is the last over This time the
ball is lifted in the air
Fielder outside the boundary line This goes for four This is a
disadvantage when the pitch falls
You do
n't get a chance to try here The ball will go for four runs
Tennis ball will dance Bounce
and go over the head Ball
four This shot A brilliant start on the first ball
Only six runs Five balls
good bowling this time No runs
This is a good comeback Arvind is
bowling now Four balls six
runs 3 d two 26 for two Adam Insurance
Brokers  Limited  To win the match now we
need a full toss ball, it has been pulled, we will definitely
go for two runs,
the distance is long enough on the leg side, by the time we
throw the second run, you will be able to run
comfortably, four runs, three balls, still
both the teams have a good hold on this match, a good battle, a good fight,
so coming up, last three balls, four to get here, we go, very good, just a very fair
delivery, absolutely
fantastic bowling
performance, no signal by the
umpire, so four to get from two balls, very
good
bowling, Nikhil Chavan, changing the course of the
match into the black hole, this is something drastic,
absolutely
fantastic, the Blue Army celebrates, still
the match judge is on, the pressure is on, Adam
Insurance, now United Strikers
strike, so 3.5
for 28, Rohit Sharma was a new better, he went back
in the
pavilion, Rohit Sharma all from
BGT towards now, this
tournament, one ball, four
required, now the new, but Dhira Sunane will take no for a duck
Striker and Nikhil
Chauhan he is a
man let's see he will become a hero if he
hits a four one ball four runs here we go he
lifted the ball in the air and caught it a
brilliant catch and with this we
won the match Uni Lite Strikers gave a
great performance here they completely
destroyed the team a good comeback low scoring
games have a lot of drama so with this we
won the match by three runs Uni
Lite Strikers one by three
runs you can see the action replay he
lifted it in the area of ​​long off and a
brilliant catch catches wins matches so
with this the first day ends we will meet tomorrow till then
subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon you will get a notification for
tomorrow's match day two will start at the end of
day one we had a fantastic day
and absolute fantastic
performance from all the teams will see you next time
tomorrow stay tuned for tomorrow Lites
are on signing of my Mit Solanki
game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lumbard Health Insurance in  The
Game of Life Stay Protected with
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance